{
    "subject": "resource/Animal_Crossing",
    "predicate": "property/game",
    "object": "resource/Animal_Crossing:_New_Leaf",
    "human_readable": "Animal Crossing is a game.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.789673924446106,
            "question": "Can you play Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7062838673591614,
            "question": "What type of thing is Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6174455881118774,
            "question": "What platforms can you play Animal Crossing on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5928240418434143,
            "question": "What kind of activities might you do in Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5884245038032532,
            "question": "Do people enjoy playing Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5690647959709167,
            "question": "What makes Animal Crossing unique compared to other games?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5565271973609924,
            "question": "Are there different versions of Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45639386773109436,
            "question": "Is Animal Crossing a real-world place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4242127239704132,
            "question": "Who created Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2710561454296112,
            "question": "Is Animal Crossing a movie or a book?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Animal Crossing is a game.",
            "html": "dbpedia_142_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who created Animal Crossing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_142_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Animal Crossing a real-world place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_142_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there different versions of Animal Crossing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_142_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_129.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_148.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_162.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_163.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_142_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}